Guide to the Bates Worldwide, Inc. Records, 1934-2005 and undated RL.00090
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials Series, 1981-2003 and undated; 43 boxes
  Conair, box PB12
  Concerta, box NB15
  Condado Plaza, box PB111
  Conference Board, box CC5
  Conoco, box NB15
  Consejo Publicitario Argentino, box CR10
  Continental Airlines, box NB15
  Cooper, Irwin, box AVO9
  Coors Brewing Company, boxes NB15, PB12, PB36
  Cordiant Communications Group, boxes AVO37-AVO38, CC84-CC86, HR11, HR49, NB2, CC66
  Corona beer, box CR26
  Corporacion INCSA, box CR40
  Corporate Angel Network (CAN), box CC23
  Corrigan, Tim, boxes AVO9, CC106
  Court TV, box NB15
  Courtemanche, Howard, box CC106
  Cousins, Geoffrey, box AVO9
  Coyne, Kevin, box CC106
  CPC International (see also Bestfoods), box CC23
  Cracknell, Andrew, box AVO9, CC107
  Crain's, box CC39
  Credit Suisse/First Boston, boxes NB15, NB16
  CricketNext.com, boxes CR29, CR35
  Croft Original Sherry, box CL118
  Crown Lager, box CR20
  Cuisinart, box NB16
  Cuisine Solutions, box NB16
  Cunard Lines, boxes CC23, CL53-CL56, PB93, PB100, PB108, PB122, PB128
  Cushman & Wakefield, box NB16
  Cutty Sark, boxes CR18, CR40
  CVS, boxes CC23, NB17, PB128
  Cystic Fibrosis, box CR28
  Dane, Max, box CL6
  D'Angelo, Art, boxes CC69, CC107
  Danish Distillers, box CR20
  Danish Rail, box CR20
  Dannon, box NB17
  Datek Online Brokerage Services, box NB17
  Datex, box CR29
  Davis and Geck, boxes PB109, PB119
  Dawn, box CC63
  DeBain, Debbie, box CC60
  Debreceni, John, box CC107
  Del Monte, box NB17
  Delaney, box CC39
  Dell Computers, box NB17
  Della Femina, Jerry, box HR41
  Deloitte, box NB17
  Delta Airlines, box NB17
  Demi-Tasse, box CL118
  Denehy, Micky, box CC107
  Dentyne Ice (see also Pfizer), boxes CL123, CL134, PB125
  Derivion, boxes CL57, PB93
  Desitin (see also Warner-Lambert), box PB118
  Deutsche Bank, box CR10
  DG Bank, box NB17
  DHL, boxes CR10, CR40, PB46A
  Dial Corporation, box NB17
  Diamond, Healthworld, and Waterloo, box CC67
  Dick-Rath, Deborah, box CL26
  DiPasca, Rodger, boxes CL27, CL125
  Discovery Channel/Animal Planet, boxes CR10, CR18
  Discovery Networks, box NB17
  Discovery.com, box NB17
  Disney: see Walt Disney, box NB18
  Dolan, Bernie, box CC107
  Dole, box PB68
  Donaldson, William, box AVO15
  Donino, White, and Partners, box CC72
  Double Click, box NB18
  Dr. Scholl's, boxes PB37, PB47, PB58
  DRM, box PB123
  DTAC, box CR40
  Dudynskay, Michael N., box CC107
  Duffy-Mott, box PB33
  Dunlop Maxfly Sports Corporation, box NB18
  Dupont, box NB18
  Duracell, box NB18
  E & J Gallo, box NB18
  E.D.S. (Electronic Data Systems), box CC23
  Earth's Choice, box CR29
  Easdon, Don, box CC107
  Eastman Kodak, box CL57
  Eazor, Joe, box CC107
  eBook (RCA), box NB18
  Eckerd, box NB18
  Eddie Bauer, box NB18
  EDS, boxes CR10, PB93, PB123, PB129
  Egmont comics, box CR40
  Eisnor, box NB18
  Electric Art, box CR20
  Electrolux, boxes CL6, PB7, PB13, PB34, PB93
  EnBW Energy, box CR29
  Endless Pain, box CR35
  Energizer, box CL6, NB18
  Energy Australia, box CR10
  Epilady, box CR51
  Ericsson Cellular, box CC23
  ESPN, boxes CC23, CC24, CR10, CR26, CR40
  Estée Lauder, boxes CC24, CL6, PB113, PB118, PB124
  ETA barbecue sauce, box CR20
  Ethan Allen, box NB18
  Europcar, box CR45
  Eveready, box CL58
  EVineyards, box NB18
  Falcon Jet, box PB99
  Farmindustria, box CR10
  Fawcett, John, boxes AVO26, AVO31, AVO38, CC56, CC107
  Federal Voting Assistance Program, box CL6
  FedEx, box NB18
  Fidelity Investments, box NB18
  Fiedler, John, box HR41
  Financial Times, box NB18
  Finesse (Helene Curtis), boxes CL3, CL4
  First Response, box PB93
  Fisher Price, boxes PB57, PB93
  Florida Prepaid College Board, box NB18
  Florsheim, box NB18
  Follow the Rabbit, box NB18
  Food Network, box NB18
  Foot Locker, boxes CC24, CL58-CL62, PB93, PB106, PB107, PB121
  Forbes, boxes CR36, CR41
  Forest Labs, box NB18
  Fortune International, box CC39
  Foster, Archie (Archibald McGeorge), box HR41
  Foster's, boxes CR29, CR35, NB18
  France Telecom, box NB18
  Frankfurter Allgemeine, box CR18
  Frank's Nursery and Crafts, box NB18
  Fresto (Warner-Lambert), box CL134
  Friends of the Earth, box CR28
  Froelich, Bob, boxes AVO26 CC107
  Fruit of the Loom, box NB18
  Frutali (Warner-Lambert), box CL134
  FT.com, box NB18
  Fuji, box NB18
  Future Kids, box CR48
  Futures @ Net, box NB18
  Gadzooks, box NB18
  Gamble, Robert, box CC107
  Gateway, box NB18
  Gaz Metropolitan, box CR12
  GE (General Electric), boxes PB93, PB130
  GECC (General Electric Capital Corporation), boxes PB99, PB110
  Geiger, Joan, box HR41
  General Felt, boxes PB101, PB111
  General Foods, boxes PB22, PB38, PB46A, PB54
  General Motors, box NB18
  Gentleman magazine, box CR10
  Gerald Stevens, box NB18
  Gilbey Canada, box CL118
  Gilette, box NB18
  GlaxoSmithKline, box CR41
  GNC, box NB18
  Go Beyond meeting, box CC56
  Goldman Sachs, box NB18
  Goldstein, Leonard, box AVO26
  Gore-Tex, box NB18
  Granath, box CR45
  Grand Bay Hotels, box NB19
  Green Mountain, box NB19
  Grey Advertising, boxes CL75-CL82
  Grignon, Perianne, box CC107
  Grolsch, box NB36
  Group Telecom, box CR41
  Groupom, box CR20
  GTE (General Telephone), boxes CC24, PB93
  Gury, Jeremy, box HR41
  Gymboree Corporation, box NB19
  Hackett, Randall, box CC107
  Haddad, box PB89
  Hahn, Carole, box CC107
  Hallmark, box NB19
  Hamill, Alex, box CC107
  Hamilton Island, boxes CR13, CR46
  Hamilton, Rich, box CC108
  Hart, Timothy, box CC108
  Hasbro Incorporated, box NB19
  HBO (Home Box Office), boxes CC24, NB19, PB23, PB39
  Health and Hospitals Corporation, box NB19
  Health Net, box NB19
  Healthmark, box CC63
  Healthworld, box CC24
  Hearn, Colin, boxes CC60, CC108
  Hearn, David, box AVO27
  Hefty, boxes PB14, PB35
  Heineken, boxes CR19, CR29, CR35, CR37, CR48, NB19
  Heinz (H.J. Heinz), boxes CL6, CR12, NB19
  Helene Curtis, boxes CL3, PB31
  Help USA, box PB118
  Herbert, Ike, box AVO11
  Hertz Rent-a-Car, boxes CL63-CL64, PB14
  Heublein, boxes PB109, PB120, PB130
  Hewlett-Packard, box NB19
  Hilton, box NB19
  Hindustani Lever, box CR20
  Hinton, Graham, box CC108
  Hire.com, box NB43
  History Channel, box NB19
  Hoefer, Dieterich, and Brown, box CC63
  Hoffman Advertising Group, box CC63
  Hoffman-La Roche, box CL69
  Hoganas Keramik, box CR10
  Holiday Inn, box PB93
  Holland House, box PB48
  Holloway Sportswear, boxes AVO1, NB19
  Holmen, Robert, box HR24
  Holten, Morgens, box AVO11
  Home Depot, box NB19
  Hoosier Lottery, box CC24
  Horton, Church, and Goff, box CC64
  House of Prince, boxes CR10, CR41
  Howard Johnson (HoJo), box PB110
  Howard Swink, box CC64
  HP: see Hewlett-Packard, box NB19
  Humphrey, Browning, and McDougall, box CC64
  Hyatt International Corporation, box NB19
  Hyundai, boxes AVO1, AVO11, CC24-CC26, CL65-CL68, CR41, CR46, PB51, PB61, PB72, PB79, PB93, PB125
  IAA (International Advertising Association), boxes AVO12, CC5
  Icon Megastore, box CR35
  IKEA, boxes CR13, CR28, CR46, NB20, NB41
  Imperial Tobacco, box CL69
  Inchape, box CR13
  India tourism, box CR20
  Indianapolis Colts (football team), box CC27
  Industrial National Bank, box PB15
  Infogrames Incorporated, box NB20
  ING Group, box NB20
  Ingalls Association, box CC64
  Instant Photo (Sony), box CL4
  Instinet.com, box NB20
  Instituto Nacional de Cardiologia Preventiva, box CR47
  Integrated Health (TAP Pharmaceuticals), box NB20
  Intel, box NB20
  Interactive Edge, box CC27
  Interland, box PB93
  International Continental Baking (ITT CBC; see also Wonder), boxes PB9, PB45
  International Olympic Committee, box NB20
  International SOS, box CR29
  Internet Security Systems, boxes CL6, PB118
  Intuit Incorporated, box NB20
  Investor and Analyst presentation, box CC57
  IRTS (International Radio and Television Society), box CC5
  Israel Ministry of Tourism, box PB111
  ISS, box PB124
  ISS (Internet Security Systems), box NB20
  Ivey School of Business, box CR29
  J&B Scotch Whiskey, boxes CL118-CL119
  J.I. Case, box NB20
  J.P. Morgan, box NB20
  Jacoby, Robert, boxes HR24, HR41
  Jador, boxes PB16, PB19
  Jaguar, box CR10
  Jamont, box CC27
  JCPenney, box NB20
  Jaret International, box NB20
  Jenny Craig, box NB20
  Jergens, box NB20
  JetBlue Airways, box NB20
  Jhirmack, box PB79
  Jimmi Taco Sauce, box CR41
  Jockey, box CR21
  Jockey, box NB20
  Joint Recruiting Advertising Program (JRAP), boxes CC27, CL6, CL69-82, CR36, NB21, PB92, PB118,
  Jones-Lundin Associates, box NB20
  Joop!, box PB87
  Jose Cuervo, box PB131
  Joseph Garneau, boxes HR24, PB24, PB38, PB54
  Juice Works (Campbell Soup Co.), box CL3
  Just diamond, boxes CR10, CR21, CR29
  Just gold, box CR29
  Just Having Fun, box NB21
  Just My Size, box NB21
  Kahlua, boxes CR30, CR31
  Kahn, Dominique, box CC108
  Kaiser beer, boxes CR22, CR23, CR42
  Kal Kan, boxes PB15, PB25, PB35, PB45, PB59, PB68, PB73, PB84, PB101, PB114
  Kapsky, Mark, box CC108
  Kaszner, Charles, box CC108
  Kaufman & Board Home Corporation, box NB21
  Kearns, W.H., box HR42
  Kellam, Alan, box CC108
  Kellogg Company, box NB21
  Kennedy, Neil, box CC108
  Kenyon & Eckhardt, box HR3
  KFC USA (Kentucky Fried Chicken), box NB21
  Kinney Shoes (Woolworth Specialty Footwear Division), boxes CC27, CL83-87, NB21, PB87, PB119
  Knisley, Patrick, box CC108
  Knockando Scotch Whiskey, box CL119
  Knoll Pharmaceuticals, box NB21
  Kobrand, Alize, box NB21
  Kobs & Brady, box CL132
  Kobs and Draft, boxes CC64, CC65, CC76
  Kool (see also Brown & Williamson), boxes CL11, CL15, PB22, PB118
  Kost, Steve, box CC108
  KPMG, boxes CL88, NB21
  Krev, Mitch, box CL27
  L.L. Bean, box NB22
  Labatt USA, box NB21
  Lady's Choice (see also Carter-Wallace), box CL39
  Lancaster, boxes PB85, PB86, PB93, PB102, PB115
  Land Rover, boxes CR21, CR22, CR31, CR49
  Land's End, box NB21
  Larson and Bateman, box CC65
  Latino marketing (Bates South), box NB3
  Laxatives, box CL40
  Lazard Freres, box CC65
  Lazarus, Kara, box CC108
  Lazarus, Shelley, box CC108
  Le Meridian, boxes CR31, CR35
  Lee, Spike, box CC60
  Lego Systems, box NB21
  Leiner, box NB21
  Leisure Planet, box NB21
  Lenz, Bob, boxes AVO13-AVO14, HR24
  Leung, Matthew, box CL28
  Levi Strauss & Co., boxes NB21, NB22
  Levine, Paul, box CC108
  Levitt, Theodore, box AVO27
  Lexis-Nexis, box NB22
  Lexmark, box NB22
  Light, Larry, box AVO41, HR42
  Lighthouse, box NB22
  Lighthouse Global Network, Inc., box CC67
  Limited Brands, box NB22
  Lindt Chocolates, box NB22
  Lipitor, box PB87
  Lojack, box NB22
  Los Angeles Dodgers, box NB22
  Loto/Moet, box CR18
  Louis Rich, boxes PB46A, PB54
  Löwenbräu (see also Miller Brewing Company), boxes CL2-CL4, PB40
  Lubriderm (see also Pfizer), box CL6
  Lucky Strike (see also Brown & Williamson), boxes CL11-CL15, PB87, PB118, PB125
  Luxottica, box NB22
  Lycos, box NB22
  Lysol, box NB22
  M&M/Mars, boxes AVO27, CC27, CL6, PB4, PB17, PB21, PB38, PB46A, PB54, PB58A, PB66, PB73, PB84, PB101, PB114
  MacLennan, Ross, box HR42
  MacQuarie University, boxes CR35, CR36
  Magnavox (North American Philips), boxes PB55, PB76, PB87, PB92
  Magnum malt liquor (see also Miller Brewing Company), box CL3
  Major League Baseball, box NB22
  Malibu, box CL119
  Mandarin Oriental Hotels, box CL6
  MapQuest, box PB130
  Marchese, John, boxes CC56, CC108
  Marconi PLC, boxes CL89, NB22-NB24
  Marine Midland Bank, box NB24
  Marriot, box NB24
  Mastercard, box NB24
  Mattel Inc., box NB24
  Maxell, boxes CL89, PB114, PB123
  Maxrate.com, box CL89
  Maybelline, boxes PB13, PB21, PB36, PB58
  Mayer, Martin, box HR42
  Mazzuchelli, Robert, box CC108
  MCA/Universal, box NB24
  McBride, Gary, box CC109
  McCaffrey & McCall, boxes CC72, CL135
  McCann-Erickson, boxes CL108-CL109
  McDonalds - Boston Franchise Group, box NB24
  McIllhenny-Tabasco, box CR21
  McKennan, Jim, box CC109
  Meadow Lea Foods, box NB24
  Media, box CC54
  Mego, boxes PB25, PB34
  Meineke, box NB24
  Meister Brau (see also Miller Brewing Company), boxes CL4, CL5, PB40
  Melanson, Anne, box CC109
  Men's Wearhouse, box NB24
  Mercedes Benz, boxes CR11, CR21, CR24, CR331, CR424
  Met Life (Metropolitan Life Insurance), box NB24
  Metropolitan Museum of Art, boxes CL90, PB75A
  MG, box CR42
  MH20, box NB24
  Michelin North America, box NB24
  Michelob (Anheuser Busch), box PB45
  Midas Inc., box NB24
  Midtown Golf, box CL6
  Midway Games, box NB24
  Militarycareers.com, box NB24
  Millennium Foundation, boxes CR16, CR28
  Miller Brewing Company, boxes CC27-CC29, CL91-CL112, PB2, PB6, PB40, PB56, PB69, PB83, PB87, PB97, PB112
  Miller High Life (see also Miller Brewing Company), boxes CL1-CL5
  Mini Cooper, box CR45
  Minute Maid, box NB24
  Mobil, boxes PB14, PB45
  Modell's, box NB24
  Mohegan Sun, box NB24
  Molson Breweries, box NB24
  Monahan, Tom, box CC60
  Monarch Pharmaceuticals (Altace), box NB24
  Monster.com, boxes AVO1, NB24
  Montgelas, Rudolph, box HR42
  Montgomery Ward, box NB24
  Morgan Anderson & Co., box NB25
  Morris, Mark, boxes AVO28, CC56, CC109, CL16, HR42
  Motorola, boxes NB25, NB26
  Mount Sinai, box CC29
  Mova Regional, box CR28
  MP Total Care, box NB26
  Mr. Hero, box NB26
  Murata Electronics, boxes CL6, CL113, CR35, PB118, PB124
  Murray, John, box AVO13
  Museum of Television and Radio, box CC5
  Music Bank, box NB26
  Mustang/Joop! Jeans, boxes PB86, PB102, PB115
  MVP.com, box NB26
  Myanmar Brewery, box CL6
  Nabisco, boxes HR14, PB13
  Nadler and Larimer, box CC66
  Nair, boxes PB87, PB118
  Napa Auto Parts, box NB26
  National Discount Brokers, box NB26
  National Geographic, boxes CL113, CR50
  Nationwide Advertising Service, box CC66
  National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), box CC29
  NCR, boxes CL4, CL5, PB49
  Needham Harper & Steers, box HR3
  Neogenic Pharmaceuticals, box NB26
  Neosporin (see also Warner-Lambert), boxes CL6, PB87
  Nestlé Purina, box NB26
  Net2Phone, box NB26
  Neupogen, box NB26
  New Moment Design, box CR21
  New World Mobility, boxes CR35, CR49
  New York Knicks, box NB27
  New York Landmarks Preservation Commission, box CC29
  New York Lottery, boxes NB26, NB27
  New York Public Library, box CC5
  New York Racing Association, boxes PB81, PB90, PB103
  New York Times, box NB27
  Newman, Richard, box CC109
  Nextel, box NB27
  Nicorette, box HR14
  Nike Inc., box NB27
  Nikon, boxes NB27, NB45
  No Regrets, box CR36
  Nokia, boxes CR11, CR18, CR23, CR24, CR28, CR32, CR35, CR49, CR50, NB27, NB43
  Norman, Craig, and Kummel, box CC66
  North American Philips (Magnavox), boxes CC29, PB55
  Northern Telecom (Nortel), boxes NB27, PB72, PB79, PB82
  Northwest Airline, box NB27
  Novartis, box NB27
  Noxell, box PB31
  Nutro Products, box NB27
  NYSE, box CC69
  NZ Cheese, box CR11
  Oakley, box NB27
  Ocean Spray, boxes NB27, PB7
  Office of National Drug Control Policy (ONDCP), boxes CC29, NB27, NB28
  Old Forester, box CL6
  Old Navy, box NB27
  Once, boxes CR33, CR35
  One Club for Art and Copy, box CC5
  Onida, box CR46
  Opensite, box CL113
  Operation Graduation, box NB28
  Opportunity in Diversity presentation, box CC57
  Optimum Online, box NB28
  Oracle Corporation, box NB28
  Organ Donation Center of Thailand, box CR16
  Origins, boxes PB110, PB126
  Orion Pictures, box CC29
  Orion Telecommunications, box NB28
  Orkin, box NB28
  Orlando/Orange Country Convention & Visitors Bureau, box NB28
  Oronite (ChevronTexaco), box CL6
  Osborn, Rick, box CC109
  Outdoor Life Network, box NB28
  Pacific Sunwear (PacSun), boxes CC29, CR33, NB28
  Paddington Corporation, boxes CL114-CL119, PB26, PB32, PB42, PB52, PB62
  Palm Bay Imports, box NB28
  Panasonic, boxes PB4, PB17, PB27, PB41, PB46A. PB47, PB59
  Papagiannacopoulos, Yannis, box CC109
  Parke-Davis, box NB28
  Parker, Osbert, box AVO28
  Parliament (Philip Morris), boxes PB53, PB63, PB74
  Parmalat, boxes CC29, NB28, NB29
  Partnership for a Drug Free America, boxes CC30, PB129
  Paster, Harry, box AVO14
  Peace Corps, boxes CC30, CL120-CL122, NB38
  Pearl & Dean, box CR13
  Pearl Drops (Carter-Wallace), box CL43
  Pearson, Steve, box AVO28
  Pep Boys, boxes AVO14, NB29
  Perrier, boxes PB110, PB126
  Person, Sarah, box CC109
  Petplace.com, boxes AVO1, NB29
  Petsmart, boxes NB29, NB30
  Peugeot, box CR13
  Pfizer, boxes CL123-CL124, CR13, PB7, PB38, PB46A, PB54, PB68
  Pfizer-Lipitor, box NB30
  Pharmacia Upjohn, box CR42
  Philips Electronics (see also North American Philips), box NB30
  Philips-Van Heusen, box NB30
  Photonica, box CR13
  Picon, Mindy, box CL114
  Pier 1 Imports, box NB30
  Piker Geroge, box PB36
  Pinkham, Richard, box HR42
  Pioneer Electronics, box NB30
  Pironen, Maria, box CC109
  Playboy Enterprises, Inc., box NB30
  Playtex, boxes NB30, PB15, PB25
  PMC-Sierra, box NB30
  PNC Bank, box NB30
  Polenguinho Cheese, box CR43
  Pond-Jones, Jay, box CC109
  Positano, box PB75A
  Potenzano, John, box CC109
  Precision Drilling, box CL6
  Prempro (Wyeth Ayerst Women's Health), box NB30
  Prescriptives, box PB117
  Presideo, box CL122
  Prevacid (TAP Pharmaceuticals), boxes CC30, NB30, PB87, PB118, PB132
  Priceline.com, box NB30
  Prime Retail, box NB30
  Pripp's Breweries, boxes CR11, CR21, CR33
  Pró Juréia, box CL6
  Proctor & Gamble (see also Clairol), box NB30
  Prodigy, box NB30
  Progress Software, box NB30
  Progressive Insurance, box NB30
  Project Hope China, box CR16
  Proplayer, box PB117
  Pro-Plus, box CR35
  Prostate Cancer Research Foundation, box CR47
  Provident Financial Services, boxes CR11, CR21
  Prudential, box CC30
  Prudential, box NB31
  Prudential-Bache, boxes PB9, PB24, PB36, PB60, PB70
  PSINet, Inc., box NB31
  Pulte Corporation, box NB31
  Purex, box NB31
  Purina: see Ralston Purina
  Pusser's Rum, box CL119
  Puttner, Gerhard, box CC109
  Quaker, box NB31
  Quantera, box NB31
  Qwest, box NB31
  R. J. Reynolds, box PB44
  R.R. Donnelley and Sons, box NB32
  Radio Corporation of America (RCA) (see also eBook), boxes NB31, PB12, PB25, PB33
  Radio Shack, box NB31
  Ralston Purina, boxes CL125, NB31
  Raw Bar, box CR36
  Rayovac Corporation, box NB31
  RCI, boxes CR11, NB31
  Re/Max, box NB32
  Reckitt-Benckiser, box NB31
  Red Cross, box NB32
  Red Lobster, boxes PB30, PB31
  Reebok International/Rockport Company, box NB32
  Reeves, Rosser, boxes AVO14, AVO28, AVO29, CC109, CC110, HR15, HR42
  Reichel, Walter, box HR42
  Relpax, box NB32
  Remy Amerique, box NB32
  Renaissance Hotels and Resorts, box NB32
  Report Card meeting, box CC58
  Resort Condominiums, box NB32
  Resume.com, box NB32
  Revista Negocios, box CR33
  Reyburn, David, box CC111
  Rezulin (Parke-Davis/Warner-Lambert), boxes NB32, PB87
  Rhone-Poulenc Rorer Pharmaceuticals, box NB32
  Richards Group, box CC66
  Ritz-Carlton, box NB43
  RJ Reynolds, box PB33
  Robertson, Mike, box CC111
  Roche-Rennie, box CR35
  Rogers, Ken, box AVO14, AVO29
  Roman, Dan, box CC111
  Rosenthal, Larry, boxes CL114-CL116
  Rover, boxes CR21, CR24, CR26, CR33, CR35, CR42
  Rowland, Michael, boxes CL116-CL117
  Royal Flying Doctor Service, box CR47
  Royal Mail, boxes CR23, CR24, CR28, CR33, CR35. NB32
  Royal Olympic Cruises, box NB32
  Rubenstein Associates, box NB32
  Ruido Group, box NB33
  Rutstein, [?], box AVO29
  Rumsmiddeldirektoratet, box CR16
  Ryder, box NB33
  S.B. Thomas Co. (Thomas's English Muffins). box CC30
  S.C. Johnson & Sons, box NB34
  Saab, box CR43
  Saatchi & Saatchi, boxes AVO16, AVO38, CC72-CC74, CC76, CC78, CC86, HR3, HR11, HR49
  Safeway, boxes CR21, HR14
  Samsonite Corporation, box NB33
  Samsung Group, box NB33
  Sanders Printup Loomis, box CC66
  Sanson-Tricard, Violaine, box CC111
  SAP.com, box CR21
  Sara Lee Coffees, box NB33
  Sara Lee Lingerie, boxes NB33, NB34
  Sauza (see also Allied Domecq), boxes NB34, PB118
  Save Our Kids, box CR47
  Savings & Loan Association, boxes CL3, CL126, PB1, PB3, PB29
  SBC Communications, box NB34
  Scaros, Dean, box CC111
  Scentstrips, box PB86
  Scheonfeld, Jay, box CC111
  Schering-Plough, box NB34
  Schick-Wilkinson Sword, boxes CL127, NB34
  Scholastic Entertainment, box NB34
  Schoning, Peter, box CC60, CC111
  Schwarzkopf, box CR26
  Schweitzer, Gary, box CC111
  Schweppes, boxes PB14, PB33, PB50
  Scunci (L & N Sales and Marketing), box NB34
  Seagate Technology, box NB34
  Sears Roebuck & Co., boxes AVO15, NB34
  Seat, boxes CR11, CR34, CR35, CR43, CR46, CR49
  Sempra Energy Solutions, box NB34
  Serta, box NB34
  Seven-Up, box PB31
  Sharp Electronics, box NB34
  Shell Oil Company, box CL6
  Sheraton, box NB35
  Showtime, box NB35
  SHR, box NB35
  Sidney 2000 Apparel, box CR33
  Silberberg, Bob, box CC111
  Silver, Jaqueline (Jackie), boxes CC111, HR42
  Silver, Jacqueline, box HR42
  Silverman, Marylin, box CC111
  Simon Project, box CC75
  Singer, Claude, box CC111
  Sky Television, boxes CR43, CR46, CR49
  Slomin's, box NB35
  Slosberg, Robert, box CC112
  Smith, Ian, box CC112
  Smith, Nancy, box CC112
  Smith, Steve, boxes CL117-CL118
  Smithkline Beecham, box CR11
  Solar Inc., box CR35
  Sole Technology, box NB35
  Sonae.com, box CR43
  Sonicare, box NB35
  Sony, boxes CL3-CL5, CL128-CL129, CR33
  Spalding Sports Worldwide, box NB35
  Speakers Bureau, box CC5
  Spectranet, box CR33
  Spectrum United, boxes CR11, NB35
  Speedy (Bates Canada), box NB35
  Speilvogel, Carl, boxes AVO15-AVO19, CC66, CC112, HR24, HR43
  Sprint, box NB35
  St. Francis Friends of the Poor, box PB75A
  St. Luke's/Texas Heart Institute, box CL6
  Stake, Marcus H., box CC112
  Standard Brands Company, box PB12
  Stanley Steamer, box NB35
  Staples, box NB35
  Starwood Lodgings, box NB35
  Starz!/ Encore (Liberty Media), box NB35
  Stavanger Museum, box CR51
  Steele, Gary, box CC112
  Stern, Les, boxes AVO31, CC60, CC112
  Stone, Marcia, box CC112
  Stora, box CR11
  Stride Rite, box NB35
  Stubbings, John, box CC112
  Sturtevant and Hildt, box CC66
  Stuyvesant Lights (Scholz and Friends), box CL6
  Suave (Helene Curtis), boxes CL3, CL4
  Sunkist Growers, Inc., boxes NB35, NB36
  Suntours, boxes CR11, CR13
  Superdrug, box CR21
  Susnjara, Gary M., box CC112
  Sydney 200 Apparel, box CR35
  Symbol Technologies, box NB36
  T. Rowe Price, boxes CC30, NB36, PB99, PB118, PB120, PB125, PB131
  T.J. Maxx, box NB36
  Taco Bell, box CR44
  Taj Bengal, box CR44
  TAP Pharmaceuticals (Prevacid), boxes CC30, PB118
  Target Corporation, box NB36
  Tarrytown Conference, box CC58
  Tatnell, Art, box CC112
  Taylor, Tony, box CC113
  TDC Mobil, box CR44
  Ted Bates Inc., boxes AVO38, AVO39, AVO41, PB11, PB20, PB33, PB37, PB48, PB59, PB126
  Teen Link, boxes CC17, HR21
  Teenage market, boxes CL29, CL31, CL33, CL34, CL49, CL50
  Telecom Malaysia, box CL6
  Tennis Canada, box CR21
  Terzis, Jon J., box CC113
  Tetra Pak, box NB36
  Texaco, boxes CC30, PB108, PB118, PB122
  Thames water, boxes CR33, CR44, CR50
  The Gap, box NB18
  Thomas' English Muffins, box CL6
  Thomasville Furnishings, box NB36
  Thompson Medical Co. (Slim Fast), box PB12
  Tickets.com, box NB36
  Tiffany & Co., box NB36
  Time, boxes CR44, CR46
  Timex, box NB36
  TMT Conference, box CC72
  Today's Press clippings, boxes CC42-CC53, NB1
  Toothpaste, boxes CL42-CL43
  Torello, Judy, boxes CC9, CC10, CC60, CC113
  Toshiba, box NB36
  Toyota, boxes CR11, CR33
  Tracy-Locke Advertising, box HR3
  Transworld Airlines, box NB36
  Trojan (see also Carter-Wallace), boxes CL6, CL43-CL50, CR35, PB118
  Truserv Corp., box NB36
  Tucker Wayne, box CC66
  Turner, Ted, box AVO16
  TV Cable Magazine, box PB39
  TV Guide, box NB36
  TWA, boxes PB91, PB95, PB95, PB104, PB105
  Tyco International, box NB36
  UDate.com, box NB36
  Ultram (Ortho-McNeal Pharmaceuticals), box NB36
  Uncle Ben's, boxes HR24, PB58A, PB68, PB85
  UNICEF, boxes CC30, CR16
  Unique Selling Proposition (USP), boxes AVO20, AVO22, AVO27, AVO29-AVO31, CC18, CC41, HR12, HR13, NB3, NB4